https://www.cch.coop/privacy-policy/

Effective: 1st May 2018
CCH is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.
This webpage tells you the data protection and privacy practices for https://www.cch.coop/, specifically:
PLAIN ENGLISH SUMMARY
We take your privacy very seriously.
Children (under 18s) are not eligible to use our services and should not submit any personal information to CCH.
CCH does not actively track you as an individual.
WHY WE NEED YOUR INFORMATION AND HOW WE USE IT
If you sign up to access parts of the website we retain this information you provide on a database in order for you to sign in and for us to identify you and the information you input onto the website.
Should you send us an email via the contact form, your name, email address and message will be emailed to us (as you would expect). This information is kept private. We will store this information within our own email system so that we are able to respond to you.
Should you comment on a blog post or web page on this site, then your name, email address, IP address and message will be stored in our website database (as you would expect). This makes your name, website address and comment (but not your email address) viewable by the general public on the website.
The website does use some cookies when you browse this website. These are used to ensure proper running of this website, and also to help us improve your experience when browsing.
We do not use 3rd Party / Tracking / Advertising cookies.
Sign up to our newsletters
Data
Use or type of processing
Why we do it
Email address
To send you emails.
You have asked us to send you emails i.e. you have provided your consent for us to do this.
Name
To personalise our communication with you.
Where we can, we want our member updates to be personalised and if you need to contact us for any reason, we can easily find and verify your record in our systems.
Organisation
To link your personal record with your co-op’s records.
Organisations not individuals are members of CCH. Some products and services we provide are only available to members, or have different pricing for members and or other groups such as commercial and not-for-profit organisations. We therefore have a legitimate interest to know where you are from, to make our communications more relevant to specific groups.
Create an online account
Data
Use or type of processing
Why we do it
Email address
To let you log in and link with your co-op’s records.
Your email address is a unique identifier. By using this identifier, we can easily link your online account with your member account if we already have your email address within our records.
Name
To ensure you are the legitimate officer for your co-op.
So that we can verify your record in our systems.
Organisation
To link your co-op’s record with our company records.
Organisations not individuals are members of CCH. We cannot give you access to the member area of the site unless your co-op is a member.
* we do not store passwords
Contact form
Data
Use or type of processing
Why we do it
Email address
To send you emails.
Email is normally the easiest way for us to contact you.
Phone number
To telephone you in relation to your enquiry.
Sometimes the most efficient way to handle an enquiry is to have a telephone conversation.
Name
To personalise our communications with you.
We do this because we know who to address our response to.
Organisation
To personalise our communications with you.
Organisations not individuals are members of CCH. Some products and services we provide are only available to members, or have different pricing for members and or other groups such as commercial and not-for-profit organisations. We therefore have a legitimate interest to know where you are from, to make our communications more relevant to specific groups.
WHICH ORGANISATION IS COLLECTING THIS INFORMATION
The Confederation of Co-operative Housing.
HOW THIS INFORMATION IS USED
If you have chosen to share it with us, we use your name, email address and username in order for you to sign in, view and use certain content and functionality on the website. We use your email address to contact you in reply to your message, or to send you our newsletter. If you have entered your email address to leave a comment on the blog, it is used to identify your comment, however it is not displayed on the website or shared with any third party.
We may also use your email to help resolve issues or disputes, for example if you tell us that you cannot see any of your posts on the website, we would probably search our database using your email address to help diagnose the problem.
OUR DISCLOSURE OF THIS INFORMATION
Information about users that sign up to the website is important for the website to function. We share your personal information for very limited reasons and in limited circumstances, as follows:
Service providers. We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to our website, such as web administrators/developers. We will share your personal information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these services.
EMAIL OPT-OUT
Just like you, we hate spam. We do not send you spam emails.
You may opt-out of our emails at any time. An ‘unsubscribe’ link is included in all of our email newsletters.
PROTECTION OF YOUR INFORMATION
CCH uses best endeavour to safeguard the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information but we do not use encryption (such as SSL) or firewalls to further protect the information as it travels across the Internet. We do not believe that the personal information we collect warrants this level of security. It is important to be aware that there is no such thing as “perfect internet security”.
HOW TO CORRECT INACCURATE INFORMATION
Once posted, you cannot change or remove any comments you have submitted on our website pages and/or posts. However, if you would like to have this information removed please contact us and we will do this for you.
You should know that because of technical constraints, all information is never completely removed from our databases. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your personally identifiable information will be completely removed from our databases in response to your requests that it be removed. We will aim to remove all publicly-facing information.
DATA RETENTION
We retain your personal information only for as long as necessary to provide you with our services and as described in our Privacy Policy. However, we may also be required to retain this information to comply with  legal and regulatory obligations, to resolve disputes, and to enforce our agreements. We generally keep your data for the following time period: 7 years.
YOUR RIGHTS
If you reside in certain territories, including the EU, you have a number of rights in relation to your personal information. While some of these rights apply generally, certain rights apply only in certain limited cases. We describe these rights below:
You may have the right to access and receive a copy of the personal information we hold about you by contacting us using the contact information below.
Change, restrict, delete. You may also have rights to change, restrict our use of, or delete your personal information. Absent exceptional circumstances (like where we are required to store data for legal reasons) we will generally delete your personal information upon request.
You can object to (i) our processing of some of your information based on our legitimate interests and (ii) receiving marketing messages from us after providing your express consent to receive them. In such cases, we will delete your personal information unless we have compelling and legitimate grounds to continue using that information or if it is needed for legal reasons.
If you reside in the EU and wish to raise a concern about our use of your information (and without prejudice to any other rights you may have), you have the right to do so with your local data protection authority.
Contacting the regulator – The Information Commissioner’s Office is the UK’s independent authority set up to uphold information rights in the public interest, promoting openness by public bodies and data privacy for individuals. If you are unhappy with our use of your personal data you have the right to complain to the Information Commissioners’ Office as the Supervisory Authority for the UK they can be contacted via their website.
HOW TO CONTACT US
Please use the contact form on this site to contact us.
CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY
From time to time we may update this Privacy Policy in line with website changes that may affect the personal information we gather about you. It is assumed that you accept such changes if you continue to use the site and services. If you do not accept such changes then you should stop using CCH’s website and services, and contact us (details above) if you would like any information removed.
Facebook PostsConfederation of Co-operative Housing (CCH)
3 days ago CCH Annual Conference 2020:
It is with great regret that we are not going to be able to go ahead with our rescheduled Annual conference at the Mercure Haydock Park in December.
The team at CCH have been closely and continuously monitoring the COVID19 situation as it has developed both globally and in the UK, and we are still not in a situation where we can risk going ahead with a large gathering.
Current restrictions are unlikely to change and many areas are in local lockdown, including that of the conference hotel itself.We are now looking at dates in the middle of next year at the same hotel and we will send out the new dates as soon as possible.
We thank you for your patience and understanding. ... See MoreSee LessView on Facebook·ShareShare on FacebookShare on TwitterShare on Linked InShare by EmailConfederation of Co-operative Housing (CCH)
3 days ago Happy #housingday! Spotlight on Bunker Housing Co-op - building their own homes means 'Importance' is at the heart' #communityledhousing www.ica.coop/en/newsroom/news/brighton-housing-cooperative-provide-homes-local-residents ... See MoreSee LessBrighton housing cooperative to provide homes for local residents | ICAwww.ica.coopAfter three years of trying to secure affordable housing, Martyn Holmes and his partner Agata Bogacka, who live in Brighton, UK, with their children, co-founded Bunker, a housing cooperative, in 2014. View on Facebook·ShareShare on FacebookShare on TwitterShare on Linked InShare by EmailConfederation of Co-operative Housing (CCH)
4 days ago Just in case you missed it:
New six-month eviction notice period comes into force ... See MoreSee LessNew six-month eviction notice period comes into forcewww.housing.org.ukThe six-month notice period came into force on 29 August and the government has issued guidance on these regulations. View on Facebook·ShareShare on FacebookShare on TwitterShare on Linked InShare by EmailConfederation of Co-operative Housing (CCH)
4 days ago More information from Anthony Collins Solicitors on the extension of the Corporate Insolvency and Governance Act allowing AGMs to be held virtually.Don't forget to update your rules - it won't last forever! ... See MoreSee LessGood news: General Meeting saving provisions are now in place until 30 December 2020www.anthonycollins.comAGM plans gone awry with re-introduced lockdown measures? Good news: saving provisions are now in place until 30 December 2020 View on Facebook·ShareShare on FacebookShare on TwitterShare on Linked InShare by EmailConfederation of Co-operative Housing (CCH)
4 days ago Are you a member of the Co-op Party?
Join Granby 4 Streets CLT for this sessionThursday 15 OctoberLunchtime Session13:00-14:00 Don’t moan, organise! Community-led high street revivalHigh streets are the beating hearts of our communities – but their decline is accelerating. Covid-19 and the threat of further lockdowns leaves much of the retail sector with an uncertain prognosis. But as panelists in this session demonstrate, the power to protect and revive our high streets and town centres is in our hands.Chair: James Murray MPHope Not HateHazel Tilley, Granby 4 Streets CLTColin Smyth, MSP for South Scotland and member of the Midsteeple Quarter ... See MoreSee LessView on Facebook·ShareShare on FacebookShare on TwitterShare on Linked InShare by Email
Contact CCH Confederation of Co-operative Housing
Registered office: 19 Devonshire Road
Liverpool L8 3TX
Telephone: 07940 448 014
Email: info@cch.coop
The Confederation of Co-operative Housing Ltd is registered in England and Wales
as a company limited by guarantee.
Registration Number 328 488 4
Membership Signup/Register Membership of the CCH is your statement of solidarity. It brings your organisation into the co-operative movement, and provides you with a direct channel through which you can help to shape the future of co-operative housing in the UK. Signup/Register
We are social
© Copyright CCH 2020 | Accessibility | Privacy Policy | Cookie Policy | Links | designed by iDC design
This site uses cookies:
Find out more.Okay, thank you
